lillypulitzer.com 2019-02-27

# Lilly Pulitzer Privacy Policy | Lilly Pulitzer

We have created this ecommerce privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your email and personal information. This privacy policy (this “Policy”) applies to your use of our mobile applications, the www.LillyPulitzer.com website (the “Website”), and our stores, which are owned and operated by Sugartown Worldwide LLC (“Sugartown Worldwide”, “Lilly Pulitzer”, “us”, “our” or “we”). Your privacy and security are important to us. Please read this Policy carefully to understand how we will use and protect the personal information you provide us. We will not share your personal information with anyone except as described in this Policy. This Policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it and under what circumstances we share it with third parties. This Policy also describes the decisions you can make about how you provide your personal information to us. If this Policy changes in the future, we will post an updated version on our website. You can tell if this Policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears at the bottom. You may change how you provide your personal information to us at any time.

## Our Privacy Policy: Contents

  * Information We Collect
  * Using Information We Collect
  * Sharing Information We Collect
  * International Users
  * Your Decisions on Receiving Marketing Communications
  * Our Use of Cookies
  * Security
  * Children's Privacy
  * Mobile Location Analytics Data
  * Use of Our Wi-Fi Network
  * Links to Other Sites
  * California Privacy Rights / Questions or Comments

## Information We Collect

We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, gender, birthday, and product preferences when engaging in any of the activities listed below:

  * Place an order from our website
  * Make a purchase at one of our Lilly Pulitzer Retail Stores
  * Return an item or make an exchange from a previous purchase
  * Inquire about our services
  * Receive a gift package
  * Create an account (profile) at LillyPulitzer.com
  * Subscribe to receive our emails
  * Enter a contest or sweepstakes
  * Are referred to us through a marketing promotion
  * Participate in a marketing survey, promotion, or event
  * Navigate to and through our website (see Our Use of Cookies below for further information)
  * Participate in Lilly Pulitzer social media including ratings & reviews and stories

For visitors who upload, post, e-mail or otherwise make available data, text, photographs, graphics, images, software, music, sound, videos, messages or other materials (“Content”) on or to Lilly Pulitzer.com; through our hashtags (such as #SummerInLilly, #Resort365, MakeItSunny or #ILoveLilly); any other website, microsite or any other internet property owned, operated or sponsored by Lilly Pulitzer (collectively “Lilly Pulitzer Sites”), you agree to and acknowledge (1) our Community Content Policy found at [www.lillypulitzer.com/customer-service/privacy-security/community-content.html](https://www.lillypulitzer.com/customer-service/privacy-security/community-content.html), (2) our use of your Content; (3) You are at least thirteen (13) years of age; and (4) we collect information you provide, including but not limited to your first and last name, email address and any additional personal information submitted with the Content. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make. We may combine all of this information with information about you that we acquire from our joint marketing partners, from unrelated third parties, and from our other brands.

This website uses Mouseflow, a third-party analytics tool, to track page content and click/touch, movement, scroll, and keystroke activity. You can opt-out at [http://mouseflow.com/opt-out.](http://mouseflow.com/opt-out)

## Using Information We Collect

To provide you with the best possible customer experience, we may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * To process and fulfill your order, including to send you emails to confirm your order status and shipment
  * To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications
  * To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions
  * To help us learn more about your shopping preferences
  * To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services
  * To enhance your shopping experience
  * To analyze trends and statistics
  * To protect the security or integrity of our websites and our business
  * To contact you
  * To improve our merchandise selection and customer service

You have the option not to receive marketing information or calls. For instructions on opting out, please see the section entitled, “Your Decisions on Receiving Marketing Communications”, below.

## Sharing Information We Collect

We may share your personal information in the following ways:

  * We may share your information with our service providers who manage our customer information and perform services on our behalf, such as fulfilling promotions, sending communications to our customers, conducting surveys, etc. We do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use or disclosure of your information.
  * We may share your information when we partner with another company in a joint marketing program to offer or provide products, services, contests, or promotions to our customers. We also work with third party companies that use tracking technologies (including cookies and tags) on our website in order to provide tailored advertisements on our behalf and on behalf of other advertisers across the internet. These companies may collect information about your activity on our sites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications and use this information to determine which ads you see on third-party websites and applications. For more information about this practice and to understand your options, please visit [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). Except for sharing this information with a joint marketing partner, we do not sell or lease your information to any third party to use for marketing their products.
  * We may share information about you, if necessary, in our good faith judgment, to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the rights of Lilly Pulitzer or others.
  * If you purchase Lilly Pulitzer products through our website or by placing a catalog order by phone or mail, we may share your name, postal address, and shopping history with like-minded organizations whose privacy policies meet the Direct Marketing Association's privacy standards, for their direct mail marketing purposes.

## International Users

Our products and services are available exclusively in the U.S. and we control and operate this Site in the U.S. Your personal information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and, by using the Site, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside your country of residence, including the U.S., which may have data protection rules that are different from those of your country.

## Your Decisions On Receiving Marketing Communications

You can review your personal information at any time. To access your personal information online, simply click Your Account at the top of any web page, sign in when prompted. You can update your personal information, by calling Guest Services at 1.888.725.4559. We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. Lilly Pulitzer provides a choice in communication for customers so you can receive information from us at your discretion. We communicate with our customers by promotional email, mailings (postal) and telephone. If you would like to be removed from our promotional email, mailings (postal) or telephone lists, please contact us by calling Guest Services at [1.888.725.4559](tel:18887254559) or by sending an email to [service@lillypulitzer.com](mailto:service@lillypulitzer.com). You may also write to us at:

Lilly Pulitzer Guest Services  
800 3rd Avenue  
King of Prussia, PA 19406

Please specify from which list(s) ? "Do Not Email", "Do Not Mail", or "Do Not Call" ? you would like to be removed from. Please note that requests by email or phone may take up to ten business days to process and request by mail (postal) may take up to six to eight weeks to process.

Alternatively, if you do not want to receive promotional emails (i.e. not order-related) that notify you of new product arrivals, exclusive offers, upcoming events, store openings and the like, simply click the unsubscribe link provided at the bottom of any Lilly Pulitzer email. Please note, however, that this is for email only.

## Our Use Of Cookies

We regularly use browser tracking cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a website. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a website or web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

We use cookies but do not store personal information in your cookie. We use cookies in order to improve your shopping experience. For example, we use cookies to:

  * Recognize you when you return to our website
  * Keep track of your order as you shop on our website and remember what items are in your My Tote
  * Process your order on our website and enable you to use Express Checkout, if you have created an account at LillyPulitzer.com
  * Study how our Guests navigate through our website and which products they request in site searches
  * Customize the message and delivery of online banner ads based on your online behavior.

Through our use of cookies, we may also track and maintain the identity of the website you visited immediately prior to visiting our website. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites.

Cookies are also used to review how visitors to our website navigate our site or interact with our email advertising. Third-party companies assist in the collection and analysis of this data. Your name, street address or credit card number is not accessed by or shared with other companies.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you decide to block cookies, our website might not function correctly. For example, if you do not allow cookies at all, you might not be able to view some of our website or use certain features like adding products to your shopping cart, which may impact your shopping experience with us. If you refuse cookies and wish to place an order from our website, please call Guest Services at [1.888.725.4559](tel:18887254559).

We work with a variety of advertising companies to place our ads on websites across the Internet. These advertising companies collect anonymous information about your visits to our web site, other advertising websites or interaction with our email through the use of cookies. This technology allows them to develop Lilly Pulitzer advertising and marketing about goods and offers that may be of interest to you.

## Security

We do our best to provide you with a safe shopping experience. We have in place certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personal information.

When you enter your personal information on our websites, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal financial information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or Location line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from “http” to “https”.

If for any reason you cannot access the secure server, or if you're not quite comfortable shopping online at any of our websites, please feel free to place your order with us through Guest Services at [1.888.725.4559](tel:18887254559).

Identity thieves sometimes send fraudulent email messages to trick customers into divulging personal or financial information (a practice known as "phishing"). "Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through email. If you have received or entered personal information in response to a suspicious email, pop-up or phony website claiming to be affiliated with Lilly Pulitzer, please call us at [1.888.725.4559](tel:18887254559) immediately.

## Children's Privacy

Protecting children's privacy is important to us. Our website is a general audience site. We do not collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is targeted to attract anyone under 13. We also do not send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13 without their parent's consent. Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any personal information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children's access to the web.

## Mobile Location Analytics Data

We may use tracking technology to collect certain information about your Wi-Fi enabled mobile device, including the presence of the device in our stores, its signal strength, its manufacturer, and a unique identifier known as its Media Access Control (“MAC”) address (collectively, “Customer Mobile Device Data”). This Customer Mobile Device Data may be collected for the purpose of determining the amount, location and frequency of customer traffic into our stores. A mobile device’s MAC address identifies a specific device to the surrounding Wi-Fi networks. The MAC address does not disclose the identity or any other personal data of the mobile device user. You may opt-out of having your MAC address recorded by visiting the following link and entering your mobile device’s MAC address: [https://optout.smart-places.org](https://optout.smart-places.org/). To learn more about the use of Customer Mobile Device Data and your choices, please visit: [http://smart-places.org](http://smart-places.org/).

## Use Of Our Wi-Fi Network

When you access our Wi-Fi, you may register with one of our service providers. Our service providers(s) may use your information to help them understand how groups of people behave, to help them and/or us provide you with a customized shopping experience, and to provide advertising of their or other third party products or services. In particular, our service provider(s) collects information that is broadcast by Wi-Fi enabled devices as well as other data from devices (e.g., web viewing and application use data, device type, device identifier, IP address (we call this other data ‘Activity Information”): (a) to create aggregated reports for their retail partners (like us) to help improve store operations and other business purposes; and (b) to allow them and/or retailers (like us) to engage directly with their visitors through Wi-Fi. Upon registration, our service provider(s) may combine information that you provide upon registration with data that they previously collected while providing services to us (dating back to July 19, 2016). Our service provider(s) collect Activity Information online and in mobile apps over time and across devices to deliver advertisements our service provider(s) think are relevant to you online, in mobile apps, and across various devices associated with you. To learn more about this activity and your choices about it, visit <http://geteuclid.com/about/privacy-statement/>.

## Links To Other Sites

Occasionally we provide links on our website to other sites we think you will enjoy. These sites operate independently of us and have established their own privacy and security policies. For the best online experience, we strongly encourage you to review these policies at any site you visit. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked websites which are provided solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.

## California Privacy Rights / Questions Or Comments

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits residents of California the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for the direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To make such a request, or for any other questions or comments please feel free to contact us at the following address:

Lilly Pulitzer Guest Services  
800 3rd Avenue  
King of Prussia, PA 19406  

Effective Date: November 1, 2017
